That's a nice smile, High Calls.
いい笑顔ですね、ハイコールズ
This is your second time, but did you get rid of your nerves?
2回目ですけど、緊張は取れました?
Yes, quite a bit.
はい、だいぶ
I got it.
取れました
It's cleaning today.
今日は清掃ですね
Cleaning JK.
清掃JKで
Can you move something?
何 か動かせる?
Can you attract it?
引き付けできる?
Cure.
キュアーって
Hello.
こんにちは
It's been a long time.
お久しぶりです
That's a nice smile, High Calls.
いい笑顔ですね、ハイコールズ
This is your second time, but did you get rid of your nerves?
2回目ですけど、緊張は取れました?
Yes, quite a bit.
はい、だいぶ
I got it.
取れました
It's cleaning today.
今日は清掃ですね
yes.
はい
Cleaning JK.
清掃JKで
A little cleaning.
ちょっと清掃
A tie also looks good on you.
ネクタイも似合いますね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
What do you think, how about your uncle's dick like this?
どうでした、このままおじさんのチンチンは?
It felt good.
気持ちよかったです
What kind of penis does Tsugu like?
つぐさんはどういうチンチンが好きなの?
What kind of dick?
どういうチンチン?
Eh, but Tsuguha, rather than just liking dick,
えー、でも、つぐは、 チンチンが好きっていうより、
I guess it's because I like things that make me feel tired.
何か奥疲れるのが好きだから、 大きいのかな?
big?
大きい?
hard?
硬い?
Can I call you thick and hard?
太くて硬いって言ってもらっていい?
Thick and hard.
太くて硬い
It's good to get tired inside.
奥を疲れるのがいいんだ
So today, let's go deep inside.
じゃあ今日、ガンガン奥に
Is it okay?
いいんですか?
vice versa.
逆に
On the contrary, it's okay.
逆に、大丈夫ですよ
Can I ask you a favor?
お願いしてもいいですか?
Is it okay to let your spirit out inside?
奥に精神を出して大丈夫ですか?
yes.
はい
Is it coming fast?
ドクドク来ます?
What happens when my friends get tired?
どうなんですか、仲が疲れると
When Naka gets tired.
仲 が 疲れると
Will I ever notice?
いつ か気づくのかな?
It's like it's in there.
入ってるのみたいな
Wasn't your heart pounding, Chin Chin?
ドクンドクンしてなかった、チンチン?
Ah, I did.
あ、してた
I was jumpy.
ビクビクしてた
Don't you feel very warm?
暖かいとかあんま感じない?
We may not know yet.
まだ分からないかもしれない
So today, let's put out a lot and get excited.
じゃあ今日、いっぱい出してドクドクね
If you feel that way, ask me to tell you that I'm excited.
そういうの感じたら、ドクドクしてるとか言ってもらって
Tell me it's okay.
いいの言って
Tsubu-san, your voice is scary, so from now on...
つぶさん、声が怖いから、じゃあ今から、
Hamenori creampie sex.
はめのり仲出しセックスします
From now on, I'm going to have creampie sex with Hamenori.
今から、はめのり仲出しセックスします
It's a little tight.
ちょっと締めてる
picture?
え?
Can it be made completely black?
真っ黒にいかせる?
Can you attract it?
引き付けできる?
touch?
触る?
Do you hate it?
嫌がるちゃう?
dislike.
嫌い
picture?
え?
Connect again.
また繋いで
Yeah.
うん
It's really cool.
すごい格好いいね
Please relax for a while.
ちょっとおなにして
Ah, this is crazy.
あ、やばこれ
Hmm.
うーん
Ah, I'm sleepy.
あ、寝そく言っちゃう
Well, say it once.
じゃあ、1回言って
Isn't it early?
早くない?
Well then, I really don't like toys.
じゃ、本当におもちゃ弱くて
That's weak.
弱いな
Ah, I'm sleepy.
あ、寝そく言っちゃう
Well then, say it once.
じゃあ、1回、言って
Isn't it early?
早くない?
Well then, I really don't like toys.
じゃ、本当におもちゃ弱くて
That's weak.
弱いな
Yeah.
うん
picture?
え?
dangerous.
危ない
Were you about to release something?
何か出そうだったの?
Are you coming out?
出るの?
No, I put it out.
いや、出したの
Can I take it out?
出してもいいの?
I'll get it out of the way.
どかすから
Tsuka-san, I'll call you right away.
つかさん、電話すぐいっちゃうから、
Let's take a picture with this.
これで撮ろう
this?
これ?
this.
これ
What is this?
何これ?
Ching Chin.
チンチン
put in?
入れる?
Please put it in.
入れてください
Ah, I like Chin Chin better.
あ、チンチンのほうが好きだもん
あ、 チ ンチ ン の ほうが好きだもん
Well then, please take this.
じゃあ、これどうぞ
Turn it.
回して
Yeah.
うん
My uncle will move it.
おじさんが動かすから
a,
あ、
While putting this in.
これ 入れながら
terrible.
やばい
picture?
え?
Shall we come out?
出ちゃう?
Let's go out.
出ちゃう
Well then, this.
じゃあ、これを
Oh, it's vibrating inside.
あ、中で振動
Let's make it vibrate.
振動させてみましょう
Turn it.
回して
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
pain
痛
Yes.
い んだよ
picture?
え?
It feels weird.
変な感じ
Isn't it good?
よくない?
Soaked.
びちゃびちゃ
Looks dangerous.
やばそう
Spread this out.
これ広げて
I might have gone.
いっちゃったかも
Can you move it?
動かせる?
Yeah.
うん
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Gachi Gachi.
ガ チガチ
Tomatilla is coming out.
トマチラ出てきてる
a little bit.
ちょっと
lick?
舐める?
I'm licking it.
舐んでる
You like this Chinchin, right?
これチンチン好きでしょ
I'm gone.
い っちゃった
Pussy and chinchilla.
まんこいまんとチンチリは
Do you like the back?
奥がいい?
I like the back.
奥がいい
Powerful?
力ある?
Looks juicy.
ジューシーみたい
It's a lot of space.
たくさん狭いからさ
back
バ ック
Do you like it?
好 きなの?
back?
バック?
Taku-chan can say it.
たくちゃんが言えちゃうんだ
Skirt, Nokoka.
スカート、のこっか
Back red from above.
上からバックレッド
From above?
上から?
From above.
上から
Follow me with all your might, I'm in.
チンチンでついて、入ってるから
It's a necktie.
肌こにネクタイです
Shall I sit down for a while?
ちょっと座らす?
No, it's okay.
いや、大丈夫
Well done, bonbon.
ちゃんと、ボンボン
Is it okay if I cum inside you?
気じょいで中出ししていい?
That's fine.
いいですよ
If I'm in a bad mood, I'll go to the back.
気じょいだと奥に出ちゃうけど
Is it okay in the back?
奥でいい?
It's fine in the back.
奥でいいよ
Chinchin, try to make yourself comfortable.
チンチン、寝心地にしてみて
Inside Chin Chin.
チンチンの中に
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
Pull it out by hand.
手 で 抜いて
Hold my hand.
手をついて
Put your hands on the bed.
ベッドに手をついて
ベ ッドに手をついて
bed.
ベッド
Like auction.
セリみたいな
Because here and here.
こことここだからね
That's amazing.
すごいね
Full inside.
中にいっぱい
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
Yeah, it felt good.
うん、気持ちよかった
good job.
お疲れ様